(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(GUNSHOTS)
Ladies and gentlemen of King's Place,
welcome to a world first possibly
in podcasting history.
Are you ready for a show?
(CHEERING)
No, not nearly loud enough, ladies and gentlemen.
Are you ready for a show?
(CHEERING)
Then, for the first and the last time,
please welcome to the stage
the cast of no such thing as a fish
as they present.
Drop us a line.
(CHEERING)
All right.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
It's hard to say how excited I think
it's been about this.
They said it couldn't be done.
They said it shouldn't be done.
They said we wouldn't sell all the tickets
and we didn't sell all the tickets.
Guys, welcome to the first ever
life-droppers of line.
You are the select few
who you'll be able to say in years to come,
I was there.
Whatever, also, we've been watched
around the world right now as well.
Around the world.
This is live streamed.
This is just, you guys are just the sort of
shock troops on the ground.
We've had information that
there are literally--
Literally, tanters of people.
(LAUGHTER)
Watch out.
Yeah.
Shout out to all our mums
and their friends.
Ah.
Just a few-- a few--
So, does anyone--
does anyone listen to no such thing as a fish?
(CHEERING)
Does anyone listen to drop us a line?
Does anyone not listen to drop us a line?
Okay.
Wow.
You are going to be called a few.
(LAUGHTER)
So, this-- you just nodded the--
Yeah.
So, this is the spin-off feedback show
from the main show, which is called--
Drop us a line.
It's got-- no.
The main show is called no such thing as a fish.
Correct.
And it's a fish pun.
So, we thought we'd--
'Cause a lot of hay, isn't it?
(LAUGHTER)
We thought it was going to be a bit bigger.
So, obviously, Drop us a line is a fishing pun
and that's why we came up with it for the feedback show.
We've been doing this show for four years now.
No such thing as a fish for 12, 12 and a half years.
And this is the most excited the crowd's ever been.
Wow.
And weirdly, what he's saying right now
is not going to be as painful as his actual introduction.
Oh, my God.
I haven't started the introduction.
No, I'm sorry.
Okay.
We should do that for the edit, of course.
Why not?
And for the audience.
And for the show itself.
Yeah.
Okay, right.
Shall we start?
Let's begin.
We've had five minutes already.
We've got so much to get through.
Okay, right.
Right.
Hello.
Welcome.
Still my thunder.
Hello, and welcome to another episode of Drop us a Line.
Woo!
Here from the London Podcast Festival at King's Place.
We've had some terrific emails over the last week or so.
You are?
My name's Andrew Ondemari.
And this is James Arkin.
Present.
And a Tisinski.
Yeah.
And Don Triba.
Sorry.
Right.
So, we're going to read out some of your emails and go home.
So, right.
So, hello.
Hello.
Cross off.
Guests.
Oh, right.
Now, good.
We've come to our first jingle.
That was actually better than most of your intros.
Yeah.
Wasn't bad.
I think you'd perform better with an audience.
I think I do.
Yeah.
Well.
Oh, you've thrown me by saying something nice about the show now.
Every time he goes for a wee and the puppy has to wait for a load of people to turn up so he can perform.
What a weird pub that would be.
Right.
Ethan's in the booth.
Sorry if I got to introduce him.
It's time, Ethan, for a rodeo clown.
I think you'll find that a rodeo clown is a very clearly defined job position.
It's a very important role in the world of rodeo.
And what it means is they're actually very well trained athletes.
And what we do is...
Jingle one, done.
Good.
Let's mark that off.
So we should say we don't know anything that's happening on this stage tonight.
We haven't heard the jingles.
We're in the same seat as you guys technically.
Yeah.
Everyone is as confused as you are right now.
What we're saying is we're distancing ourselves from that last few seconds.
I enjoyed it.
Thanks, Ethan.
Well, we've had a few emails about one particular subject, which is what a rodeo clown is.
That's why we've had lots...
I've said it already, I've said it.
So you may not have had the later show yet, which was recorded in Sweden in the city of Lund.
And we've had several emails.
Crystal Aura.
Oh, what a funny name.
What?
But both have spelled differently, weirdly.
To...
Well, 'cause Crystal's not spelled the same as Aura.
Oh, sorry.
Okay.
Got to listen to the end of a sentence before.
No, no, no, no.
Thank you all for an enjoyable evening and London last night.
We realise you're all incredibly busy people.
But please, tell us that Andy is okay.
We were seriously worried.
Oh, yeah.
Christina Fawles.
Hope you're okay, Andy.
Well, okay, let's...
So Andy decided to accept a challenge that James presented, which is...
James was given what is the hottest candy technically in the world, I guess.
Yeah, I paid for it, I bought it.
And I thought, Andy might like to try it out.
Yeah.
It's called Satan's Toe.
And it was 9,000 times stronger than the jalapeno.
I think 9 million Scoville...
I don't know, I don't really know what it means.
I didn't believe in the Scoville scale before I started sucking on that toe.
I think we have an image of what happened...
There we go.
Yeah.
And then I think we have a second image of what happened a few seconds later.
Yeah, yeah.
So, thank you everyone for your concern.
It was absolutely fine in the end.
It was, yeah.
But it hurt you for the evening, didn't it?
But you were fine in the morning.
I was fine in the morning.
And I've brought along.
I thought it'd be fun to do a little mouth challenge for you three.
Okay.
Yeah.
So...
Who would like to taste Selena Gomez's purple Oreo?
Oh, yeah.
Only if it is a euphemism.
Can you explain what this is while I get it out?
So Oreo did a collab with Selena Gomez.
And we talked about it because I think some animals were attracted to it or something?
Possums.
Oh, they use the bait possums in New Zealand.
Yeah, but they put, did they put poison in it or something for the possums?
Yeah.
And so...
We're going to play Selena Gomez Oreo Roulette.
Joe O'Malley, thank you.
You sent us a packet of possibly in date Selena Gomez Oreos.
Wow.
And, um...
Oh, they're not in date.
I'm willing to give it a go.
Yeah.
If it's more than a decade out, I'm usually a no, but aside from that...
Three dates on here.
It's got to be the last one, which is the important one.
There were three...
Wait, you don't know how to read a best before day.
Well, it's a kiwi one, so it's all confusing.
It's 25, 26, and then 2030.
Who knows?
Anyway.
They work on three different calendars, don't they, over there?
Right.
And these are, or aren't poison, sorry?
Well, I've just opened them.
So they can't be.
They don't come poison, don't they?
They're on an angle.
Let's go do some Foley.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, that's enough of that.
Are they nice?
It's very nice.
It tastes like...
You know, if you get like a chocolate chip cookie, but it's been out for a long time and it's gone soggy.
Yes.
It tastes bit like that.
I'm getting cinnamon.
I'm getting a lot of cinnamon.
Yeah.
There is cinnamon on the packet, yes.
Well, done me.
I should get a professional food tester.
Yeah.
You gave them these Selena Gomez.
I'm tasting a lot of that, and I'm loving it.
I actually...
I don't know who she is, but I'm loving it.
You don't.
I vaguely have heard of her, though.
Great.
Just to reassure people.
All right.
Well, that was our format point for the show.
So now it's free play.
Very exciting.
I just want to share...
This is really dumping her in it.
One of our colleagues sure remained nameless when I was explaining to her what we'd done to Andy,
almost killed him on stage.
And I said he was given a suite that was 9,000 times hotter than...
No, than a jalapeno.
I think it was 9,000 times hotter than a jalapeno.
She said, "A jalapeno is not that hot."
Did you hear the other bit, though?
Yeah.
9,000 times hotter than a chip is still hot.
Now it's time for another format point.
I tricked you.
There was actually more than one format point.
It's time to get yourself off the hook.
Oh.
Icelanders don't need an app to prevent a check.
What can take you?
What's the stretch of it?
Oh, the horse ran out.
Yeah, the horse ran out.
The horse ran out.
Very nice.
Okay, so this is where we've made a mistake.
And you, someone has written in.
Yeah.
And you're going to tell us about it.
But you can get yourself off the hook.
Not the fishing pond there.
What's your name?
Finley.
Finley, lovely.
Just because we'll be--
Finley.
Oh, my.
Oh.
Is he a plant?
No, he's a fish.
Everything is a fish pond.
Right.
If you dredge low enough, we've just--
What have we said next?
Right.
Dave from Zambia writes.
Cool.
Wow.
Just wanted to point out that once again, once again, James--
Oh, yeah.
--has attributed the biscuit cricket sledge to Shane Warn.
Oh.
While Shane was a well-known and much loved character
in the cricket world, the biscuit sledge was made
by the Zimbabwean Spinbola Edo Brandes.
Okay.
And the retortion in the audience.
So I'm not going to say the full punt.
And basically, he said-- someone said, why are you so fat?
And he said, because when I make love to your wife--
Very good.
--it gives me a biscuit.
Ah, yes.
And I've always heard that for being from Shane Warn.
But of course, it's a powerful, possibly even from this person.
Yeah.
It's the best way I'm going.
Dave from Zambia, thank you.
Yeah.
Brilliant.
Okay.
I accept it.
Tick.
90% of the great quotes in the world are attributed to Mark Twain
or Shane Warn.
Yes.
Right, you ready for another?
James has got himself off the--
Yeah, yeah.
No, you didn't get yourself off the hook.
Happily wriggling away on the hook.
No, you're not on the hook.
Right.
Brett Fuyings writes, in a recent little fish,
the famous Aussie Lord Howard Walter Florey was mentioned
for his work on penicillin.
He shared the 1945 Nobel Prize for Physiology or Medicine.
Feels like you could have edited this down a little bit, Brett.
But then again, so good eye before I read it out.
For his role in the purification and development of penicillin.
Understandably, James said he had never heard of him.
Florey.
But as a reputed Aussie, Dan's lack of knowledge is puzzling.
Dan would have touched Florey dozens, if not hundreds of times,
in his visits to Australia, Dan did live there for some time.
So, you know, you're Aussie.
I'm Aussie.
Florey was featured on the front of the Australian $50 banknote, Dan.
I never saw that kind of cash.
Well, he was also on the 1998 $1 coin.
The year after I got there.
So, I was familiarising myself with a lot of new things at that point.
I'm the one who brought him up on the show.
I'm the one who told the story.
But I'm the one being accused of not having heard of him.
You know what I think might have happened here, Andy?
Is someone's mistake, could you, for Dan?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, okay, yeah.
He's off the hook.
(Laughter)
So, Sam Hewitt writes,
"In episode 125 of No Such Thing as a Fish."
So, roughly 10 years ago now,
you made a grave mistake on the topic of venomous mammals.
In the episode in question, you confidently stated
that slow lorises are the only venomous mammals in the world.
However, the platypus is another venomous mammal native to Australia.
I would have thought you would have known this as it is a basic fact.
(Laughter)
I am severely disappointed in you, Andy, as a person.
But I am more disappointed in Dan.
Oh, here we go.
You literally lived in Australia, Dan.
Yeah, you have both failed me.
Thank you, Sam.
I was on the $10 note.
Yeah.
I go a cool little tip, though.
That's reminded me of a cool tip,
which is my wife's sister, Annabelle, is an actor.
And if she's ever playing an Australian,
the way that she kicks herself into the Aussie accent
is to say, "Venomous snakes."
And that, apparently, is such a good pairing of words
to get you into the flow of a Aussie accent.
Give it a go.
I didn't work when you did it, and you were on Australia.
No, Venomous snakes.
Very nice.
Oh, people are interested.
Yeah, you see.
You want some more?
No.
Venomous snakes.
Wow.
Did it work?
Venomous snakes.
That's good.
Broder, broder.
Are we still allowed to do accents?
Ooh, don't know.
Podcast@QI.com.
Yeah.
We're not allowed to do accents.
Right.
You go on.
I was just thinking that the Australian accent
will be the last to fall.
But then I remembered my husband's Australian,
and he will divorce me if he ever is me doing one.
So maybe it won't be.
Is he not streaming this live?
You did literally send him a link just before we went downstairs.
I'm going to do something you're going to enjoy.
There's no way he'll have switched off already.
There's just no way.
Right.
Can we have a bonus, Breem?
Yes.
Yeah, sure.
So Breem, finley, of course, kind of fish.
It's not really a pun, though, is it?
Not a pun at all.
Well, we're not on the section naming section yet.
Don't worry, guys.
We'll get there.
Stop hustling me, everyone.
Am I allowed to talk, or is there a brilliant jingle about to come?
No, we don't.
They don't all have jingle.
OK.
So bonus, Breem, is where we've talked about a subject
and someone sent in extra material about it.
Yes.
That's right.
And not that note.
It is faster without the jingle, isn't it?
You're all skeptical, but I think they all need a jingle.
But they don't all have one.
It's just being on it.
Sorry.
Let's hear the evil.
Well, it's funny, because it's going to give us all the tools to use on you, Australian accents.
Olivia Ayers, like The Rock.
That's weird.
I had noticed that.
I don't think we call it that anymore.
Well, Olivia Uluru writes.
Olivia Uluru writes.
Hello.
I've got to cut these down.
I was listening to your most recent episode where you talk about the grain fields Christopher
Nolan used for interstellar.
Then about Russell Christophe forget the Christopher Nolan bits, not relevant.
And then Russell Crowe running through a field of wheat.
And then Russell Crowe's hand in those wheat fields.
And the bonus bream that Olivia adds is that it is not Russell Crowe's hand.
It's a stunt double.
No.
Yeah.
Does he have hideous hands?
They're so big.
They're so big that it would have made it look like a field of crest.
I think that was the point.
Yeah.
They should have used a field of oil seed rape.
And then he would have looked like he had normal hand signs.
Yeah.
But anyway, and I looked it up and it's true.
But it's simply that a camera.
No, really Scott.
Really Scott.
Yeah.
Just noticed the stunt double running his hand through some wheat.
And he thought, oh, that's a rather nice shot.
So it wasn't actually written in the.
No way.
Unplanned.
The highlight of that film.
I know.
Wow.
Yeah.
So that's good, isn't that.
That's a good fact.
Good fact.
I wonder if that hand has got other work now.
Definitely.
There's another bonus bream from Sam McLaren blade.
Do you remember we talked about Bartolomeo Christopher Lee?
Yes.
I know the name.
Who was he?
Remind us.
He made the work.
He invented the piano.
piano.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
So Sam points out, we, and in fact, all of us here,
will have heard an instrument by Christopher.
A specific, not just any piano.
A specific piano he made.
Right.
So there's a famous piano.
And a famous piano piece that we all know and love,
which comes from one of his instruments.
Exactly.
Except I haven't read the Holy Molyette.
So actually it's a cello that he made.
But.
Yeah.
And Sam, I should say, is a violin dealer and archivist,
which is a pretty cool job to have.
Nice.
So anyway, he works for a company called W.E. Hill and Suns.
And they have an archive of all the instruments they've sold,
going back 150 years.
Incredible.
And one of the cellos by Christopher,
which passed through this company,
was owned by the Medici.
Then it was owned by Pope Pius IX.
Then Count Ferretti of Cortina.
And then it was owned by the private secretary of the Duke of Westminster,
Charles French.
None of that is relevant because in 1956 it was sold to a man named Norman Jones.
Norman Jones in 1966 was part of a string ensemble in Eleanorigby
and Strawberry Fields Forever.
Really?
Is there a cello in that song?
Yeah, it's all of us, James in the room.
We'll know.
There's a string bit in there.
It's basically orchestral throughout the song.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
I know a little rental of a man's car.
Mush car on.
That's a line.
That's the only Beatles song that I like, which is the frog song.
Not a Beatles song.
I thought that was a really good email.
That's a great email.
Sometimes it's funny the live audience changing things because you know you're expecting everything to be really hilarious.
And sometimes it'll just be cracking information like that.
Yeah. We've had an aim of this. This is on the subject of Hitler's breasts.
I don't know if you remember this.
Wait, so this was something we said about a pull up to sneak female hormones into Hitler's face, right?
Yeah.
Into him through his carrots.
Carrots.
To make him nicer.
No.
To make him feminine.
To make him grow breasts.
So people would make fun of him.
Exactly.
To make him a laughing stock.
So Hen writes in.
Hen says.
I know the answer to the, oh, James, sorry, Hen says.
James asked about the question of the size of Hitler's of natural breasts.
And whether it would be correlated to the amount of estrogen he consumed.
Yes, that's what I did ask.
I know the answer to this question as I take estrogen as part of a medical transition.
So the amount of estrogen doesn't control the eventual size of the breasts.
That is genetic.
So you have to consider the breasts of Hitler's sister.
To stop considering the size of the breasts of Hitler's sister.
That's the best way to approximate where you'd end up.
Did he have a sister?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you must have seen photos.
I mean, you've been reading a lot of that Hitler's.
I have, yeah, yeah.
I haven't been looking through the big book of monkey facades of Hitler's sister, though.
I'm interested in the sort of the war stuff.
Anyway, yeah, I just watch World War II for the war stuff.
Not in it for the books.
Go back a second.
Go back to that trouble.
Hitler's sister.
Anyway, and the fact is, Hen also knows about the process the time it would take.
And it turns out that the process typically takes between three to five years to complete.
But it can be as long as eight to ten years.
So this would not have been a war-winning strategy because it was six years of the war.
So they might have well have done it in the first day of the war, but they just hadn't seen the results yet.
Exactly, yeah.
Well, never know if Hitler was going to get massive boobs.
Yeah.
What, is that tragedy?
Well, I think the whole war was a tragedy rather than a single element like this.
And you wouldn't choose to extend it just to find out if he was going to be a double-decap, would you?
But anyone?
No.
I think it gets the time machine.
It goes back in time to save Hitler just to see.
Trust me on this one, guys, you won't regret it.
You killed him as a baby, yeah?
Actually.
Flip open to the middle of that book.
Wow, double-deeds!
Aren't you happy?
Are you happy with that?
Okay, that's cool.
It's time now for another section as we move on to an audience favourite, probably.
Spicy meat.
Here's where we get to the spicy meat.
That's the meat.
Oh, this is.
Spicy meat.
Yeah.
Spicy meat, alley.
All right.
Spicy meat.
This is the spicy meat.
I'm still not sure what spicy meat is.
Spicy meat.
It's like...
I don't need to explain this.
Spicy meat.
Maybe there's some spicy meat looking in here.
I mean, do you think there's meat?
There's someone that's using that to their sex sound trend.
That's spicy.
Oh, what was that dancing, Andy?
I would say, if anyone was too aroused after thinking about Hitler's sister,
that would have fixed things right away.
Oh, don't.
I've just lost a contact lens.
Oh, my god.
Oh, no, it's all right, it's back.
So, anyway, we're out of time for the show now, sadly.
So, spicy meat.
Is spicy meat time?
So, I've forgotten actually what spicy meat is.
Rare instance, where there's just no fish pun here.
And it's never really been clear what the section is.
It's sort of hot goss.
Arguably, the last email that Hitler's breast should have been spicy meat.
But it wasn't.
A lot of emails are sort of in the middle of a Venn diagram, aren't they?
Tell me about it.
Yeah.
We're going to come on too later about the categorization of emails, don't worry.
OK.
Right, this is one for James.
Elliot Covitz writes in,
"I was listening back to episode 592.
James mentioned he hasn't worn an iron shirt since he left a proper job 25 years ago."
OK.
"I think that's more or less true."
Right.
According to Wikipedia, James was 47 at the time he says this.
Assuming that he left his proper job to join QI 21 years ago, he's included a source.
That means he had 26 years total of non-QI life,
at least 22 of which were almost certainly spent being a child,
getting a physics degree, and qualifying as an accountant.
He's mentioned the latter two on the podcast, and the first I've presumed.
What was the first being a child?
Big big child.
Anyway, this leaves him with maximum four years to be an accountant,
work in a hotel, work in a restaurant, be the landlord of a pub,
and probably other things that I've forgotten, though I am a devoted listener.
How did he do this?
Does time move at a different speed for him?
Does he just get bored easily and change shops often?
Does he get fired?
Spicy meat.
I feel like I'm on question time.
Well, all those things are true,
and a lot of them happened in the same place,
so I could be an accountant, and what were the other things that I was...
I've crossed it out there.
I don't want to give too much weight.
Hotel restaurant.
Some of those were all in the same place,
and some of them were all in a second place.
There were two main jobs, but I had many hats above them.
You weren't in a hotel that was also a restaurant in a pub.
Yeah, but then I also worked in a accountant for a set of pubs.
So I'm actually double-pubbing it.
But I worry that we're going to peel back too much of the onion of James.
It's not really much to say.
What was this about before in a shirt?
An iron shirt, last time we weren't iron shirt.
It was just because that gave away how long it is since you had a real job,
and it turns out it's right next to you being a child.
I've seen it.
Anyway, I've probably had a proper job for like five years.
That's good.
I think that works out earlier.
I hope you're happy.
We're halfway through the show.
Has it flown?
Any thoughts or reflections as we head into the second half?
Anything you want to mix up with the second half?
Oh, yeah.
We've got a lot to get through.
I know, I'm just trying to work out.
I can't make you have pre-read the emails now, can I?
We could have a break for me to read the emails, but it'll take a while.
All right.
And then you could just do the rest of the show to us in the dressing room.
That's a good idea.
I think these guys have a drink.
Yes.
Now let's go.
Okay, let's move on to another section.
Ethan, I'm going to need a track number two.
Please track number two.
Fish fight.
Cuffs.
This poor tackle box fight.
Right hook was the name that we landed on for that one.
It was, actually, but I forgot to write it down.
Row, row, row, row your boat.
Row, row, row your boat.
Row, row, row, row.
I think it's going to be Siemens Squabbles.
Yay!
Welcome to Siemens Squabbles!
Why rule Britannia?
I don't write the jingles.
How much?
Out of interest, how much of our budget for this did you spend on these jingles?
With deepened debt.
So, this is actually not quite Siemens Squabbles.
Siemens Squabbles, uh, Finley is.
Siemens is in sailors, of course, and Squabbles is in disputes.
But we had a lot of emails about, um, seemingly stuff.
And so, I've bolted that into a new section of Siemens Squabbles.
As in sperm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Obviously. Right. Lin Lim in Geneva.
I'm on my second lesson through the fishback catalogue.
And just came across episode 393.
Oh, so it's, it's Old Siemens.
Wow.
Yeah, Squabbles.
James says to write in, if you know how mouse sperm is extracted.
Wow.
I'm excited.
Uh, much less amusing than the skip you related options suggested on the show.
Basically, mouse sperm donors are dead.
I've got to read the emails.
I've got to read them in advance.
And then, is it like electrolysis on the testicles?
Probably. Probably.
I have personally dissected genetically engineered lab mice to collect the epidid amies.
Happy-ditty mouse, my like.
Brilliant.
It's, it feels like they must have been euthanized for another reason.
You can't. Otherwise, why aren't they just masturbating in mouse?
It's like, uh-huh.
Who's not going for that job?
In this economy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No good point.
Yeah.
So there we go.
So the answer is prozeric and quite morbid, as Lin Lim says.
But that's the first email in this section.
The second one comes from Clement de Menezes on the most recent drop as a line.
So we're now in a drop as a line spiral, which is great.
Uh-huh.
You discussed, uh, Clement says pug in dissemination.
I think it was pig in dissemination we discussed.
You don't want to get those mixed up.
Oh, no.
Although it feels like someone has, when you look at a pug, no offense.
If there are any pugs in the audience.
Well, they're a bit mixed up.
Well, they look like pigs, don't they?
Yeah, they're the closest dog in, in aesthetic to a pig, maybe.
Yeah. Or maybe a bulldog?
No, but I think a pug.
So maybe that's why they're called the pug.
Probably.
Almost certainly.
We don't, and it's, it's so nice flying by well without facts and research, I think.
Yeah.
Uh, James asked about the corkscrew vagina of a sal.
Uh-huh.
Seems like I'm a bit obsessed.
But it is over 12 years.
Yeah, this is exactly.
And whether it affects the, uh, insemination straw.
As a former swine herd.
I can tell you, you get pig insemination straws with rubber screw heads.
Also, you can't freeze, again, pugs seem, but I think it's pigs.
I mean, I don't think...
I think, if it's a swine herd, who's written it, probably it's pigs even.
Yes.
You can't freeze pigs even for insemination as it reduces its potency.
So you do have to have a lot in the fridge.
And I'd suggest to Andy that he puts his food above it in case the bag splits.
Oh, okay.
Wait, so what was the question?
You were asking whether the insemination straws have to be spiral.
Yes, and they do.
And they do.
And they do. They have spiral.
There are, there are, you know, yeah.
Cool, like one of those fun, like kid straws you get at a, at a soft play or something.
Yeah, yeah.
All the beer hat straw?
The beer hat straw.
You could double up with one of them if you've lost your insemination straw, I guess.
Absolutely.
It's been a crisis.
Cool.
Let's plow on.
Two questions.
We don't have a name for this.
So if anyone would like to suggest a name for the question section,
but we're never going to do this live event again.
So, it's a limited utility.
But if anyone comes up with a good fish, a question pun, please shout it out.
Okay.
We've been sent in questions just to give us more to work with.
We've been sent two questions.
Okay.
Thanks so much.
So there are other 120 of you who have been-
I'm going to start coaching you.
Read the fucking email.
Let's send this.
Elliot.
You emailed in.
Yes.
Thanks very much.
I love your show.
Thank you very much, Elliot.
Thank you for sticking with it so long.
I would like to say thank you all for sticking with this so long.
Hey, Q and days, what is days, which is a type of fish?
Q and days.
Yes.
Is it?
Days is a kind of fish.
I would say it's a sort of category.
Oh, sorry.
Q and rays.
Oh, very nice.
Yeah.
Q and rays.
Fantastic.
Yeah.
Ruthering.
Angling for an answer.
Angling for an answer is very good.
It's quite similar to drop us a line.
But that's not a bad thing because they're all meant to be about the same thing.
So sorry.
There is going to be some overlap in theme.
Yeah.
Angling for an answer.
Q and rays I'm going to go with.
Oh.
Q and days.
Sorry, James.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll write down Q and days.
Is that what you think?
Q and days.
Days.
A-C-A-C-E.
It's a kind of fish.
Oh, it's your roommate because it's in.
I know, right.
It's in Tidler.
The children's book isn't it.
Is it?
It's a little fish and days.
Oh, yeah.
Any further offers.
Question sharks.
Oh, like question marks.
Very nice.
That's all like question time.
But it is about question.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's my favourite.
Question sharks.
What's your name?
Jessica.
I'm going to write Jessica next to that.
Start making the jingle, Ethan.
So, Elliot.
Sorry, Elliot.
We're halfway through your email.
Oh, yeah.
Here's the question.
I was getting through the bit where you said,
"I'm coming to your live recording of "Drop us a Line" in London,
and I'm so looking forward to it.
I'm sorry about how it's turned out.
(LAUGHTER)
It's any consolation.
I'm having the hour of my life here.
(LAUGHTER)
I really wanted to send in a question for you guys.
So here it is.
Who gets edited out the most?
And why?
(LAUGHTER)
You've mentioned before the show being cut down,
but is there a particular person who gets edited out most for any reason?
And coughed down, closed brackets.
Wow.
Sorry, let's get into it.
Well, Dan, you edit this show.
Yeah.
And definitely Andy gets edited out the most.
Which is weird.
Yeah.
And sorry that your question didn't make it in the show as well.
(LAUGHTER)
Ah.
On this show, on this show, on Jewel,
it might be you, Andy, purely out of the fact that you're reading a lot of emails there.
Yes.
But the main show is the main question.
Yeah, the main show I don't think there's anyone who gets cut out more than the rest, to be honest.
Well done.
A diplomatic answer, so it's not to make this even more awkward than it is.
(LAUGHTER)
Whoever speaks the most on the day would get cut out the most,
because they try and make it as even as possible.
If it's obvious that one person is speaking a bit more than they get cut shorter.
There was a really cool bit of tech that was suggested.
I think it was trialled for Zoom meetings where the more you spoke, the bigger your picture got.
So if you're in music, isn't that amazing?
That's really good.
So you can literally see, "I'm like, fuck, I'm troning on and on, aren't I?"
Was it adequate for loon like?
Was it adequate portion?
Your head?
Yeah, yeah, it turned like pinky in the brain guy.
Yeah. Some people would just think that's absolutely appropriate that I'm bigger than everyone else.
As in, if you're the kind of person who talks over everyone else in a meeting,
you're going to think, "I should be bigger."
Yeah.
And it's not just the big people that we should judge.
The person who's tiny, tiny, like a little postage stamp in the corner also,
are you contributing anything to the company?
You know, so I think you've got to look at yourself if you're too small or too big.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Good to have a go at the little people as well.
Yeah.
Nice.
That's how someone had a go at the little people.
All right. So there you go. There's your answer, Elliot.
Andrew Bond, I think you said you were present.
Hi, Andrew.
I'm just going to read out your email.
For all, no such thing as a fish is.
What subject are you desperate to find a fact about but can't find anything interesting?
Oh, interesting.
That is a good one.
That's a good question.
I'll tell you one thing.
We recently did a show which had one of the facts had two angles to it.
And in the show itself, we only covered half of it.
We never covered the second half.
So I have like a full page of research that was never used.
And I think it was about paramedics.
So I'm looking for another fact about paramedics so that I can suggest it.
And then reuse that material I don't have to do the research.
But you haven't looked endlessly and found that there's nothing interesting about them.
Not yet.
No.
For me, it's the band wet, wet, wet.
Is that a joke?
No.
I thought it might be for Finley's benefit.
That's all fish living water.
Yeah.
No, I've done extensive research on them.
Why are you so desperate to find a fact about that?
A few years ago I wrote my book, right, which is all about the weirdnesses that people have.
You should say the name of the book.
It's called The Theory of Everything else.
And it was about the intersection between the famous paperback audiobook in America.
It's been translated into multiple languages.
Into American.
Yes.
Wow.
It's taking ages.
Right.
Yeah, they've added 600 dudes into that copy.
What I did was, there was one, I guess, slightly interesting fact that they're connected to,
which is that when their song "Love Is All Around" got big because of the four weddings and a funeral soundtrack,
it made so much money that they had to take themselves off the chart because they didn't want to be hated by listeners,
who were just being hit by it as a number one.
And I think they had another single coming out, didn't they?
Yeah.
And they wanted people to buy that one instead.
Exactly.
And also, what that meant, though, was that they didn't write that song.
It was written by another guy who wrote the song "Wild Thing."
I think I love trucks.
The trucks in the trucks.
And he used all of that money to open up a radio and TV station to talk about aliens.
And so I thought, oh, I wonder if the wet, wet guys are interested in that at all.
And I spent, I think, like, a good month trying to find anything interesting about them.
And I couldn't.
And that's not a knock.
They're just leading normal lives.
But, yeah.
They, I mean, they might be fascinating, but they just haven't put it on the internet.
There you go.
I would say it's hard is to find really amazing facts about things that are already just in the public eye weird and mental.
Like, I remember when we did many years ago when we were all teenagers, the TV show where we were covering the news.
And we did, we researched the American election, which was Hillary Clinton, versus Donald Trump.
And had to do some research.
I don't know that one.
Go.
Don't remember.
But Trump is a hard person to research, right?
Because he's so insane.
Oh, yeah.
No offense to anyone.
I'm not saying I'm making a political statement there.
I'm just saying he says weird stuff.
So it's quite hard to find something that's surprising.
Because you say, oh, Donald Trump's actually got 19 toes.
And people would say, oh, whatever.
He's mad anyway.
Right.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah, I do know what you mean.
Researching a huge subject that's very present in the news is.
Well, and that's very weird.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm so sorry.
We've got 26 more pages of emails.
Yeah, no, no.
We're going to have to.
Sorry.
Sorry for answering your questions.
Well, can you not monopolise the conversation?
Sorry.
Apologise.
Let's move on to Ethan.
We need number nine, please.
If that's ready to go, because it's time for--
It's time for extreme fish.
Lovely.
Yes.
Cool.
Wow.
It's a bit of a dip in energy.
That's the 2/3 mark, don't worry.
We'll get through it.
And we'll end very, very strong.
Don't be alarmed.
So extreme fish is where someone has been listening to the show
in an extreme environment.
Exactly.
Or where they may yet.
So not really a pun.
Extreme fish.
Enrique Duran, who has written before writes,
"I forwarded your email to my astronaut friend,
because Enrique had a friend who was not a real astronaut,
but an astronaut in training."
OK.
So he's not been to space, which is the marker
when you become an astronaut, you know?
But partly so, he knew I was disclosing our private chats.
It turned out that ever since I first asked him,
if he was a listener, he has been listening to fish.
Cool.
And we-- because we've never had anyone listen in space.
I then asked him if he would promise to listen to the show in space.
And he officially vowed to listen to at least one minute of fish
during his first mission.
Cool.
So we're going to make it to space.
When's he going up?
Oh, I don't think we've got a--
well, Enrique doesn't say.
Right.
He might never.
One minute.
Why so stingy?
At least.
At least one minute.
OK.
I hope it's not the minute where you say
that he's not an astronaut, but an astronaut.
Good point.
But by then, he will be.
And I'll happily retract.
All right.
Seth Anonymous writes,
"I have what is to my knowledge, a new entry in the category of extreme fish.
Two days ago, I listened to you all while I was having a vasectomy."
Oh.
That's the exact opposite of my thought you were going to say.
[LAUGHTER]
What, an extra set of testicles grafted off?
This should be in seamen squabbles.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, it should, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh.
It was very surreal.
I will say the procedure did distract somewhat from my ability to follow the fun facts.
But it was nice to have something to laugh at while the doctor was handling my most sensitive bits.
So there you go.
Mm-hmm.
Laughing kills pain, right?
Laughing kills pain.
That is a thing.
So you wouldn't even need the anesthetic.
No.
[LAUGHTER]
No thanks, Doc.
I've got no such thing as a fish.
Oh, now it's dropping the line.
Give it the laughing.
[LAUGHTER]
We actually recommend more feed for a standard listening experience.
Oh, dear.
There we go.
And anonymous Ruth writes it.
I know you've had people listening to Fishwell giving birth,
but I thought you might like to know you're keeping company at the start instead.
And that's because Ruth is expecting a baby grow up.
Thanks for the distraction while I throw up for the second week in a row.
While I work my way through my first trimester.
Nice.
And again, the throwing up may simply be a consequence of drop us a line.
Yeah.
So that's good, isn't it?
That's some nice new extreme fish.
Yeah, I love that.
We're really racking them up.
So any more extreme fish is out there, please do let us know.
It's podcast@ky.com.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
Let's move on to Mike Giggler, no jingle.
This is just when someone sent in a joke.
And they're always very disappointed that we didn't make it on the day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Chris Locke writes, "Your recent discussion about Karl Marx being related to the Phillips toothbrush company."
Okay.
Do you remember the guy who founded Phillips was basically cousins or second cousins of Karl Marx?
Yeah.
And we had some, you know, we joked about awkward conversation at family events about dental hygiene.
This would never have happened.
Marx wouldn't have had a socialist doctrine about healthy teeth.
Because he believed proper teeth is theft.
A bit worrying that the actual bad joke got the best reaction from my crowd.
So far.
Chris ads.
If you read this out, it'll be my hat trick.
Three email sent and three read out.
And I can retire with a 100% success rate.
So congratulations, Chris.
You are free to stop listening to the podcast.
Bad luck to the rest of you.
Yeah.
It's time for quick fire.
Because we're running out of time incredibly.
We're going to have to skip a, skip a section.
I'm so sorry.
We're going to have to skip catfish corner.
Can we skip the bit where things are named after what?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll just point out, Ethan, we're going to skip this image.
But James is on to something, says Naomi R.D.
The owner of the world's oldest cat says long life is down to feeding it only Buckston spring water.
Sorry, not only Buckston.
What it says actually feeding that only Buckston mineral water for the last decade.
Oh, alongside lots of trees.
Anyway, the cat is 31.
31.
No, liar.
Apparently equivalent to 146 human ears, which is just rubbish.
Anyway, whatever it is.
Right, we're going to plow on to Dan's business suite.
New section.
Wow.
Helen Terry writes, just got back from an amazing trip to Santorini.
The views were awesome in every sense of the work.
We covered what Santorini recently on the Breast Arby episode.
Yeah.
Something else that inspired all was driving by a cafe in Emborio.
I think I actually gasped.
No one else in the car cared or had any idea why I was so excited.
It was closed for the summer, but it's a real place and it's doing incredible things.
The cafe is a Laurel and Hardy themed cafe in Santorini.
Oh, wow.
I think we have a picture of it here.
Yep.
It's got Laurel and Hardy written on it.
The insides are incredible.
They're full of Laurel and Hardy clobber.
If you stand in front of it, does it fall down and your head just pops up through it?
Yeah, it does.
It does look like it's flat and would do that.
Yeah.
You go in through the top window.
Was Dan called into consult?
Is he a silent investor?
Dan once opened up a...
I helped open up.
I was just part of the process.
A Laurel cafe and a Hardy...
I can't remember which way it was now.
Ice Cream Piler in Kosovo back in 2003.
Yeah.
And Laurel and Hardy statues were everywhere in Kosovo.
I was in Kosovo this year and I can tell you, those statues no longer exist.
So I don't know what...
I don't know if they had a moment like we did in this country where they just put them all in the river or something.
Yeah.
They're in the Epstein files, Laurel and Hardy.
Right, look, we've got a plow on, guys.
Two in email from Louis Shankar, who points out there as a company called Beron Zomatic,
who make gas burner torches and other things that burn.
And they are named for their founder Otto Burns.
That's right.
It's time for the book.
It's time for the name section, Ethan, plate number three.
Another fucking name that's not the name that you thought it was the name of.
Please, Andy, I don't know.
And that's the best one, yeah.
It's due to taste, Joe has been working on the jiggles, edited out, you say, "I'm going to shoot myself at the end of that."
That was the sentence.
I said after you gave me a different sentence to say, "For the jingle."
That wasn't the line.
That was the outtake of me genuinely going, "Andy, if you make me..."
Ah, so there we go.
Yeah.
We had an email from about Bird's Eye, which used to have a logo with a bird and its eye, but of course his named after Clarence Bird's Eye.
So that is an example of that for the book.
But that, interestingly, that email came in from a guy at Nomad Foods, grouphead of category development, whose name is Mark Bacon.
So what's going on there?
I don't know.
Just a relatively coven certain name.
He wants sort of food companies, and he's on category development, which I don't need to explain to all you guys.
But that's nominative determinism, as opposed to...
Yes, I'm saying we've got nominative determinism, and the birds are the thing for the book in the same email.
Are we allowing that in the book? Because presumably the logo is a bird's eye because... No, it's the next book.
No, no, no, sorry.
Mr Bacon's not getting in. He's out.
But the bird's eye is the logo because he's called Clarence Bird's Eye, right?
Yeah.
So I don't think we can allow that in the book.
Yeah, sorry. I'm just checking what we've...
I know. We have to do a thousand and one of these.
Yeah, it's a good point.
Everything's going in.
We're in injury time now.
Let's just have jingle number four, please, Euth.
You mean Harkin.
Just a good jingle. Don't want to leave it on the table.
Is that it?
That's it.
And now...
That's how we're good.
With one minute to go in the chat.
And I have that jingle for my own personal use.
You certainly can, of course.
Thank you.
Huge thanks to Joe Mayo, who's worked on a lot of these emails.
Joe, Delilah Leigh and Ethan have all contributed massively to them.
I'm doing the credits before the outro. Sorry, right.
Oh, let's crack on.
We've got one last point to make, which is about Frank Hoffman.
Do you want to see Frank's massive egg that he found?
Of course.
Thought you might want to hear about a recent event in our backyard chicken coop.
Get this.
Frank found a jumbo egg, which was so big because it had another egg inside it.
Holy moly.
I've really cut down the email, by the way, guys, because it's a very detailed email.
Isn't that nuts?
Well, that is incredible.
This, it turns out, Frank writes, is a very rare event caused by reverse peristalsis.
Sending the egg the wrong way up goes back up, I think.
And another egg forms around it and then it comes out.
That's amazing.
It's very rare, says Frank.
No kidding.
That is a climax worth staying for.
I think.
Look at that.
Frank.
So that's just a really big weird egg that we...
That wasn't really related to anything we do.
No, it shouldn't really be in the show, but I couldn't.
No.
Boy, you're going to leave that out of the show.
I'm not going to leave that out.
No, come on.
That's gold.
Isn't that good?
It's really wonderful, actually.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's get the Humpty Dumpty jingle and get out of here.
So that's the end of the show, everybody.
Yeah.
Yeah, mixed.
Well, yeah.
That's, yeah.
I think if Anna ever does get that time machine,
maybe you should use it just to give them their hour back.
How do we think it's been?
Yeah.
Finley's happy.
Nice.
Are you going to do a proper wrap-up?
Yeah, I'll do a proper wrap-up.
Right, so that's it for this episode of Drop as Align.
What a fun experiment is being.
And that's why you do experiments sometimes.
They don't get published.
Yeah, you have to publish your normal results.
Yeah.
That's very important in science.
Absolutely.
No, this has been magical, guys.
Thank you so much for being here for the first of many live,
drop us the live experiences.
Yeah.
And if you have been affected by any of the issues...
(LAUGHTER)
...raised in this show, just email podcast@qy.com.
Maybe you've got an extreme fish.
Maybe you've experienced a seamen squabble.
Maybe you want to get one of these guys on the hook.
Maybe you're a rodeo clown.
Maybe there's... I'm just reading them all out now.
But whatever it is, please email it to podcast@qy.com.
Yeah, or even if it's nothing to do with any of those things,
then it's just a big egg.
Why don't I set that in?
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah.
You section, big egg of the week.
That's part of it.
So, thanks so much as always to Dan, Anna and James,
who've played really well.
(APPLAUSE)
All right. Congrats to you.
Thank you, Andy.
You're rating this all.
Yeah.
So, just nothing else would be to say really.
Thank you and sorry, I suppose.
Thank you, sorry, and goodbye.
Thanks, everyone. See you next time, bye.
(APPLAUSE)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(upbeat music)
[BLANK_AUDIO]